<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Technology - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/technology/</link><description>Technology - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</managingEditor><webMaster>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/technology/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Illusion Serverless &amp; Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</guid><description>Die Illusion von Serverless Funktionen in der Cloud Einleitung Ich bin enttäuscht, wie oft das Marketing über den gesunden Menschenverstand siegt. Viele Manager setzen sich über ihre eigenen Experten - die Entwickler. Das gilt auch für die Migration in die Cloud. Spoiler: Wer Geld sparen muss, sollte die Cloud meiden. Denn das neue Buzzword &amp;ldquo;Serverless&amp;rdquo; in der Cloud bedeutet: Du kümmerst dich um die Software, wir kümmern uns um die Hardware.</description></item><item><title>Back to Maven?</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 01:01:01 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</guid><description><![CDATA[Back to Maven? 10 years of Gradle. The elusive quest for simplicity and a short journey to rediscovering the power of Maven. Maximising Developer Potential We need more time-saving tools Topics that are often overlooked or rarely discussed interest me. Often cool technologies are in use, but hardly anyone talks about the problems associated with them. Development has become very time-consuming these days. With cool buzzwords like &ldquo;serverless&rdquo;, &ldquo;low code&rdquo;, &ldquo;IaC&rdquo;, &ldquo;Big Data&rdquo;, &ldquo;Cloud&rdquo;, &ldquo;DevOps&rdquo;, &ldquo;You Build it You run it&rdquo; etc.]]></description></item><item><title>The Unspoken</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 01:01:01 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</guid><description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Unspoken&amp;rdquo; Decide for yourself what is true for you and what issues you prefer to look away from.
I dare to explore the forbidden realms of development and want to push boundaries and challenge conventions. Uncovering the extraordinary in the world of development. Technology should make our lives and work easier.
Only the bravest among us really manage to make development easier for others.
When was the last time you completed a project that was virtually maintenance-free, robust and no longer needed you?</description></item></channel></rss>