<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Technology - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/technology/</link><description>Technology - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</managingEditor><webMaster>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/technology/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Hype</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/ai_behind_the_hype/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/ai_behind_the_hype/</guid><description>AI in the Real World - Going Beyond the Hype Introduction When it comes to the adoption of Artificial Intelligence (AI), there is a lot of hype and high expectations. Some believe that AI will revolutionize the workforce and render human capabilities obsolete. However, before diving headfirst into the world of AI, it is crucial to consider some key points. Undoubtedly, AI has made significant advancements, but it is not a new concept and comes with significant limitations that we need to understand and respect.</description></item><item><title>Illusion Serverless &amp; Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</guid><description>The illusion of serverless functions in the cloud Introduction I am disappointed how often marketing wins out over common sense. Many managers put themselves over their own experts - the developers. This is also true when it comes to migrating to the cloud. Spoiler: If you need to save money need to save money should avoid the cloud. Because the new buzzword &amp;ldquo;serverless&amp;rdquo; in the cloud means: You take care of the software, we take care of the hardware.</description></item><item><title>Back to Maven?</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</guid><description><![CDATA[Back to Maven? 10 years of Gradle. The elusive quest for simplicity and a short journey to rediscovering the power of Maven. Maximising Developer Potential We need more time-saving tools Topics that are often overlooked or rarely discussed interest me. Often cool technologies are in use, but hardly anyone talks about the problems associated with them. Development has become very time-consuming these days. With cool buzzwords like &ldquo;serverless&rdquo;, &ldquo;low code&rdquo;, &ldquo;IaC&rdquo;, &ldquo;Big Data&rdquo;, &ldquo;Cloud&rdquo;, &ldquo;DevOps&rdquo;, &ldquo;You Build it You run it&rdquo; etc.]]></description></item><item><title>The Unspoken</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</guid><description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Unspoken&amp;rdquo; Decide for yourself what is true for you and what issues you prefer to look away from.
I dare to explore the forbidden realms of development and want to push boundaries and challenge conventions. Uncovering the extraordinary in the world of development. Technology should make our lives and work easier.
Only the bravest among us really manage to make development easier for others.
When was the last time you completed a project that was virtually maintenance-free, robust and no longer needed you?</description></item></channel></rss>