<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Technology - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/technology/</link><description>Technology - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</managingEditor><webMaster>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/technology/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Risks of the Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/risks_of_cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/risks_of_cloud/</guid><description>Risks of the Cloud - Why You Should Think Twice Introduction The hype about the cloud is impossible to ignore. From small startups to large corporations - everyone is raving about the flexibility, scalability, and simplicity of the cloud. But just like Icarus burned himself when he flew too close to the sun, companies that move to the cloud without thinking could also experience dangerous pitfalls.
Costs and Transparency The cloud world may appear attractive, but high costs often hide behind the shiny facade.</description></item><item><title>Test Levels: Finding the Right Balance</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/test_level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/test_level/</guid><description>Test Levels: Finding the Right Balance The given markdown text is already in English, hence, there&amp;rsquo;s no need for any translation: Introduction The topic of testing still seems to be uncharted territory with a lot of room for interpretation to this day. The traditional test pyramid has been questioned and new test pyramids have emerged. In my opinion, there is no need for a test pyramid, but a clear understanding of what needs to be tested.</description></item><item><title>AI Hype</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/ai_behind_the_hype/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/ai_behind_the_hype/</guid><description>AI in the Real World - Thinking Beyond the Hype Introduction When it comes to the use of Artificial Intelligence (AI), there is a lot of annoying excitement as well as expectations. Some believe that AI will revolutionize the world of work and make human capabilities redundant. But before we dive headfirst into the world of AI, we should consider some important points. AI has undoubtedly made progress, but it is not new and comes with considerable limitations that we must understand and respect.</description></item><item><title>Illusion Serverless &amp; Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</guid><description>The Illusion of Serverless Functions in the Cloud Introduction I&amp;rsquo;m disappointed with how often marketing triumphs over common sense. Many managers overrule their own experts - the developers. This also applies to the migration to the cloud. Spoiler: those who need to save money should avoid the cloud. For the new buzzword &amp;ldquo;Serverless&amp;rdquo; in the cloud means: You take care of the software, we take care of the hardware. However, if you have a capable, motivated and curious administrator, you can run Serverless yourself (e.</description></item><item><title>Back to Maven?</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</guid><description><![CDATA[Back to Maven? 10 years of Gradle. In search of relief and a short journey to the rediscovery of the strength of Maven. Maximizing the Potential of Developers - We Need More Time-Saving Tools Topics that are often overlooked or rarely discussed interest me. Often there are cool technologies in use, but hardly anyone talks about the problems associated with them. Development has become very complex these days. With cool buzzwords such as &ldquo;Serverless&rdquo;, &ldquo;Low Code&rdquo;, &ldquo;IaC&rdquo;, &ldquo;Big Data&rdquo;, &ldquo;Cloud&rdquo;, &ldquo;DevOps&rdquo;, &ldquo;You Build it You Run it&rdquo; etc.]]></description></item><item><title>The Unspoken</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</guid><description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Unspoken&amp;rdquo; Decide for yourself what is true for you and what topics you prefer to look away from.
I dare to enter the forbidden areas of development and uncover the extraordinary in the world of development. Expand your horizon and push your limits. Always remember, technology should make our lives and work easier.
Only the bravest among us really manage to simplify development for others.
When was the last time you completed a project that was practically maintenance-free, robust, and no longer needed you?</description></item></channel></rss>