<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Cloud - Tag - &lt; The Unspoken ></title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/tags/cloud/</link><description>Cloud - Tag - &lt; The Unspoken ></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</managingEditor><webMaster>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/tags/cloud/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Risks of the Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/risks_of_cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/risks_of_cloud/</guid><description>Risks of the Cloud - Why You Should Think Twice Introduction The hype about the cloud is impossible to ignore. From small startups to large corporations - everyone is raving about the flexibility, scalability, and simplicity of the cloud. But just like Icarus burned himself when he flew too close to the sun, companies that move to the cloud without thinking could also experience dangerous pitfalls.
Costs and Transparency The cloud world may appear attractive, but high costs often hide behind the shiny facade.</description></item><item><title>Illusion Serverless &amp; Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</guid><description>The Illusion of Serverless Functions in the Cloud Introduction I&amp;rsquo;m disappointed with how often marketing triumphs over common sense. Many managers overrule their own experts - the developers. This also applies to the migration to the cloud. Spoiler: those who need to save money should avoid the cloud. For the new buzzword &amp;ldquo;Serverless&amp;rdquo; in the cloud means: You take care of the software, we take care of the hardware. However, if you have a capable, motivated and curious administrator, you can run Serverless yourself (e.</description></item></channel></rss>