<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Software - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/software/</link><description>Software - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</managingEditor><webMaster>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/software/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Illusion Serverless &amp; Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</guid><description>The illusion of serverless functions in the cloud Introduction I am disappointed how often marketing wins out over common sense. Many managers put themselves over their own experts - the developers. This is also true when it comes to migrating to the cloud. Spoiler: If you need to save money need to save money should avoid the cloud. Because the new buzzword &amp;ldquo;serverless&amp;rdquo; in the cloud means: You take care of the You take care of the software, we&amp;rsquo;ll take care of the hardware.</description></item><item><title>Back to Maven?</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</guid><description>Back to Maven? The markdown text is already in English, and it contains a markdown image with a hyperlink to an article titled &amp;ldquo;Moving Back from Gradle to Maven&amp;rdquo; on the website phauer.com.
10 Years of Gradle. In search of relief and a brief journey to rediscover the strength of Maven. Sorry, there is no text to translate in the given markdown code. It seems to be an empty code block.</description></item><item><title>The Unspoken.</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</guid><description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Unspoken&amp;rdquo; Decide for yourself what is true for you and which topics you prefer to ignore.
I dare to explore the forbidden areas of development and uncover the extraordinary in the world of development. Expand your horizon and push your limits. Always remember, technology should make our lives and work easier.
Only the bravest among us truly succeed in making development easier for others.
When was the last time you completed a project that was practically maintenance-free, robust, and no longer required your attention?</description></item></channel></rss>