<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Software - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/software/</link><description>Software - Category - &lt; The Unspoken ></description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</managingEditor><webMaster>nova@scene.to (Nova Annabella)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/categories/software/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Illusion Serverless &amp; Cloud</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/illusion_serverless_cloud/</guid><description>The illusion of serverless functions in the cloud Introduction I am disappointed how often marketing wins out over common sense. Many managers put themselves over their own experts - the developers. This is also true when it comes to migrating to the cloud. Spoiler: If you need to save money need to save money should avoid the cloud. Because the new buzzword &amp;ldquo;serverless&amp;rdquo; in the cloud means: You take care of the You take care of the software, we&amp;rsquo;ll take care of the hardware.</description></item><item><title>Back to Maven?</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/back_to_maven/</guid><description><![CDATA[Back to Maven? 10 years of Gradle. In search of relief and a short journey to rediscover the power of Maven. Maximizing the potential of developers - we need more time-saving tools Topics that are often overlooked or rarely discussed interest me. Cool technologies are often in use, but hardly anyone talks about the problems associated with them. Development has become very costly these days. With cool buzzwords like &ldquo;serverless&rdquo;, &ldquo;low code&rdquo;, &ldquo;IaC&rdquo;, &ldquo;Big Data&rdquo;, &ldquo;Cloud&rdquo;, &ldquo;DevOps&rdquo;, &ldquo;You Build it You run it&rdquo; etc.]]></description></item><item><title>The Unspoken</title><link>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Nova Annabella</author><guid>https://novaannabella.github.io/the_unspoken/</guid><description>Welcome to &amp;ldquo;The Unspoken **Decide for yourself what is true for you and what topics you prefer to look away from. I dare to explore the forbidden areas of development and uncover the extraordinary wants in the world of development. uncover. Also expand your horizons and push your boundaries. Always remember, technology should make our life and work easier. **Only the bravest among us truly succeed in making development easier for others.</description></item></channel></rss>